[{
    "question": "`13-2`",
    "answer": ["`11`", "`3`", "`6`", "`10`"],
    "correct_answer": "`11`"
},
{
    "question": "`15-4`",
    "answer": ["`11`", "`4`", "`9`", "`5`"],
    "correct_answer": "`11`"
},
{
    "question": "`12-10`",
    "answer": ["`2`", "`5`", "`3`", "`1`"],
    "correct_answer": "`2`"
},
{
    "question": "`14-3`",
    "answer": ["`11`", "`9`", "`12`", "`8`"],
    "correct_answer": "`11`"
},
{
    "question": "`15-5`",
    "answer": ["`10`", "`5`", "`9`", "`7`"],
    "correct_answer": "`10`"
},
{
    "question": "`16-7`",
    "answer": ["`9`", "`8`", "`11`", "`10`"],
    "correct_answer": "`9`"
},
{
    "question": "`19-2`",
    "answer": ["`17`", "`15`", "`3`", "`6`"],
    "correct_answer": "`17`"
},
{
    "question": "`20-3`",
    "answer": ["`17`", "`14`", "`5`", "`7`"],
    "correct_answer": "`17`"
},
{
    "question": "`15-4`",
    "answer": ["`11`", "9``", "`2`", "`13`"],
    "correct_answer": "`11`"
},
{
    "question": "`10-7`",
    "answer": ["`3`", "`6`", "`9`", "`4`"],
    "correct_answer": "`3`"
},
{
    "question": "`16-4`",
    "answer": ["`12`", "`8`", "`4`", "`10`"],
    "correct_answer": "`12`"
},
{
    "question": "`19-6`",
    "answer": ["`13`", "`7`", "`2`", "`14`"],
    "correct_answer": "`13`"
},
{
    "question": "`17-4`",
    "answer": ["`13`", "`12`", "`9`", "`6`"],
    "correct_answer": "`13`"
},
{
    "question": "`16-2`",
    "answer": ["`14`", "3``", "`12`", "`6`"],
    "correct_answer": "`14`"
},
{
    "question": "`18-4`",
    "answer": ["`14`", "`12`", "`8`", "`6`"],
    "correct_answer": "`14`"
},
{
    "question": "`15-7`",
    "answer": ["`8`", "`9`", "`4`", "`12`"],
    "correct_answer": "`8`"
},
{
    "question": "`8-5`",
    "answer": ["`3`", "`4`", "`2`", "`7`"],
    "correct_answer": "`3`"
},
{
    "question": "`18-5`",
    "answer": ["`13`", "`9`", "`7`", "`16`"],
    "correct_answer": "`13`"
},
{
    "question": "`19-13`",
    "answer": ["`6`", "`4`", "`9`", "`5`"],
    "correct_answer": "`6`"
},
{
    "question": "`17-9`",
    "answer": ["`8`", "`11`", "`6`", "`2`"],
    "correct_answer": "`8`"
},
{
    "question": "`18-7`",
    "answer": ["`11`", "`9`", "`3`", "`12`"],
    "correct_answer": "`11`"
},
{
    "question": "`17-5`",
    "answer": ["`12`", "`11`", "`6`", "`4`"],
    "correct_answer": "`12`"
},
{
    "question": "`14-8`",
    "answer": ["`6`", "`8`", "`4`", "`10`"],
    "correct_answer": "`6`"
},
{
    "question": "`7-2`",
    "answer": ["`5`", "`9`", "`6`", "`7`"],
    "correct_answer": "`5`"
},
{
    "question": "`5-1`",
    "answer": ["`4`",  "`2`", "`1`", "`6`"],
    "correct_answer": "`4`"
},
{
    "question": "`6-3`",
    "answer": ["`3`", "`1`", "`9`", "`4`"],
    "correct_answer": "`3`"
},
{
    "question": "`10-1`",
    "answer": ["`9`", "`11`", "`7`", "`3`"],
    "correct_answer": "`9`"
},
{
    "question": "`9-2`",
    "answer": ["`7`", "`11`", "`9`", "`3`"],
    "correct_answer": "`7`"
},
{
    "question": "`4-3`",
    "answer": ["`1`", "`7`", "`2`", "`4`"],
    "correct_answer": "`1`"
},
{
    "question": "`5-5`",
    "answer": ["`0`", "`1`", "`10`", "`11`"],
    "correct_answer": "`0`"
},
{
    "question": "`6-2`",
    "answer": ["`4`", "`2`", "`8`", "`6`"],
    "correct_answer": "`4`"
},
{
    "question": "`8-3`",
    "answer": ["`5`", "`11`", "`2`", "`3`"],
    "correct_answer": "`5`"
},
{
    "question": "`5-4`",
    "answer": ["`1`", "`9`", "`0`", "`6`"],
    "correct_answer": "`1`"
},
{
    "question": "`8-2`",
    "answer": ["`6`", "`10`", "`4`", "`12`"],
    "correct_answer": "`6`"
},
{
    "question": "`10-3`",
    "answer": ["`7`", "`13`", "`5`", "`1`"],
    "correct_answer": "`7`"
},
{
    "question": "`6-5`",
    "answer": ["`1`", "`11`", "`2`", "`6`"],
    "correct_answer": "`1`"
},
{
    "question": "`7-3`",
    "answer": ["`4`", "`10`", "`3`", "`6`"],
    "correct_answer": "`4`"
},
{
    "question": "`10-5`",
    "answer": ["`5`", "`15`", "`10`", "`0`"],
    "correct_answer": "`5`"
},
{
    "question": "`9-4`",
    "answer": ["`5`", "`13`", "`3`", "`6`"],
    "correct_answer": "`5`"
},
{
    "question": "`8-5`",
    "answer": ["`3`", "`11`", "`9`", "`14`"],
    "correct_answer": "`3`"
},
{
    "question": "`6-6`",
    "answer": ["`0`", "`12`", "`3`", "`5`"],
    "correct_answer": "`0`"
},
{
    "question": "`10-6`",
    "answer": ["`4`", "`16`", "`12`", "`8`"],
    "correct_answer": "`4`"
},
{
    "question": "`8-7`",
    "answer": ["`1`", "`15`", "`3`", "`6`"],
    "correct_answer": "`1`"
},
{
    "question": "`10-4`",
    "answer": ["`6`", "`14`", "`10`", "`12`"],
    "correct_answer": "`6`"
},
{
    "question": "`9-7`",
    "answer": ["`2`", "`16`", "`4`", "`6`"],
    "correct_answer": "`2`"
},
{
    "question": "`8-8`",
    "answer": ["`0`", "`16`", "`1`", "`7`"],
    "correct_answer": "`0`"
},
{
    "question": "`10-4`",
    "answer": ["`6`", "`14`", "`4`", "`8`"],
    "correct_answer": "`6`"
},
{
    "question": "`12-4`",
    "answer": ["`8`", "`16`", "`12`", "`4`"],
    "correct_answer": "`8`"
}]